Guide to the Isabella Gonzalez collection, 2006-2017 MS 928
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Isabella Gonzalez collection
2006-2017
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Gonzalez, Isabella
MS 928
1.5 Linear Feet (3 boxes)
The Isabella Gonzalez collection mainly consists of materials collected and created by Gonzalez during her time at Rice University. A large portion of the collection is photographs, contact sheets, and negatives.
Biographical / Historical
Isabella Gonzalez, a native Texan, graduated from Rice University May 2013 with an Electrical and Computer Engineering degree. She obtained a master's degree in the same field from the University of California, Santa Barbara.
After graduation, she founded Zither AI, a software platform that analyzes television and film scripts.
Content Description
The Isabella Gonzalez collection mainly consists of materials collected and created by Gonzalez during her time at Rice University. A large portion of the collection is photographs, contact sheets, and negatives. The collection also contains correspondence and ephemera saved during her time at Rice.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Isabella Gonzalez in 2020 and 2021.
Index Terms
Subjects
Music; Social life and customs; Hispanic Amercan college students; Jews and Jewish life
Document Types
photographs
- Series I: General files
  - ARTS Courses, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Children's Prison Arts Project (CD), 2006-06-26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2009-2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Germany ephemera, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Houston phemera, 2010-2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - New York ephemera, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Off campus housing, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rice University ephemera, 2010-2013 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Texas ephemera, 2010-2013 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Series II: Photographs
  - Brown College, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - General photographs, 2009-2012 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Houston, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Mandell Park, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Rice University, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - SXSW Austin, 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Series III: Contact sheets, negatives, CDs
  - Contact Sheets, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Negatives, 2010-2017 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Photograph CDs - New York, 2012-03 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Series IV: Books
  - Final Book for Arts 381, 2010-12-02 (Box 2)
  - Monsters by Ken Dahl, 2009 (Box 2)
- Series V: Memorabilia
  - A Beer Bike T-shirt, 2011 (Box 3)
  - Chinese Student Association T-shirt, 2011 (Box 3)
  - RJCE ECE T-shirt, 2011 (Box 3)
  - Duncan College T-shirt, 2012 (Box 3)
  - German Academic Exchange Service [DAAD] bag, 2012 (Box 3)
  - Hack Rice T-shirt, 2012 (Box 3)
  - Michael B. Dye tie-dye T-shirt with explanation, 2012 (Box 3)
  - Michael B. Dye black T-shirt with explanation, 2012 (Box 3)